TusCon Records Collection 1974-2014
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
TusCon Records Collection 1974 – 2014
MS 561
De Priest, Carol
The TusCon Records contains materials related to the TusCon Science Fiction Convention from its beginnings with the first convention held in 1974 up to 2014. The collection also contains materials and ephemera from various other science fiction conventions that TusCon co-founder Carol De Priest (1943 - 2015) attended. The collection is divided into two series: TusCon Convention Materials and Other Science Fiction Convention Materials.
6 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/ E-Mail: LBRY-askspcoll@email.arizona.edu
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Biographical Note
TusCon is an annual regional science fiction and fantasy convention held in Tucson, Arizona. Beginning in 1974, TusCon has had a convention every year except during the years of 1977 - 1978 (referred to as TusCon 5), as both cofounders, Carol De Priest and Jim Corrick, took that time to work on IguanaCon/WorldCon in Phoenix, Arizona, The convention considers itself to be fan-oriented and has been able to bring in big names in the science fiction and fantasy community, such as Jim Butcher, Diana Gabaldon, and George R. R. Martin.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into 2 series
Series I:TusCon Materials, 1974-2014
Series II: Other Science Fiction Convention Materials, 1972-2011
Scope and Content Note
The collection (1974-2014), contains materials including convention programs, agendas, badges, pins, newspaper clippings, and correspondence related to the convention as well as other nearby science fiction conventions including IguanaCon, LepreCon, and L.A. Con.
Access Terms
De Priest, Carol.
Science Fiction.
Fantasy.
Conventions.
Tucson -- Arizona.
Container List
- TusCon Materials, 1974 - 2014; Series 1
  Arranged chronologically, this series contains the programs, schedules, administrative paperwork, and ephemera that was collected during TusCon until 2014. Though it started out as bi-annual for the first three conventions, it eventually turned into annual conventions after TusCon 3. The majority of folders provide materials on each of these yearly conventions. However, not every convention has a folder; those conventions lacking folders still have materials for those years in Box 2, within the binders of TusCon ephemera.
  - TusCon 1, October 25, 1974 - October 27, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - TusCon 2, April 4, 1975 - April 6, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - TusCon 3, November 7, 1975 - November 10, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - TusCon 4, November 5, 1976 - November 8, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - TusCon 6, November 6, 1979 - November 9, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - TusCon 7, November 7, 1980 - November 9, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - TusCon 8, November 13, 1981 - November 15, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - TusCon 9, November 12, 1982 - November 14, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - TusCon 10, November 18, 1983 - November 20, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - TusCon 11, November 9, 1984 - November 11, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - TusCon 12, November 8, 1985 - November 10, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - TusCon 13, October 3, 1986 - October 5, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - TusCon 14, October 2, 1987 - October 4, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - TusCon 15, October 7, 1988 - October 9, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - TusCon 19, November 13, 1992 - November 15, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - TusCon 20, November 13, 1993 - November 14, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - TusCon 21, November 11, 1994 - November 13, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - TusCon 22, November 3, 1995 - November 5, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - TusCon 23, November 15, 1996 - November 17. 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - TusCon 24, November 7, 1997 - November 9, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - TusCon 25, November 6, 1998 - November 8, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - TusCon 26, October 22, 1999 - October 24, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - TusCon 27, November 10, 2000 - November 12, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - TusCon 29, November 15, 2002 - November 17, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - TusCon 30, November 14, 2003 - November 16, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - TusCon 31, November 5, 2004 - November 7, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - TusCon 32, November 10, 2005 - November 12, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - TusCon 33, November 18, 2006 - November 20, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - TusCon 34, November 9, 2007 - November 11, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - TusCon 35, November 7, 2008 - November 9, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - TusCon 36, November 13, 2009 - November 15, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - TusCon 37, November 12, 2010 - November 14, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - TusCon 38, November 11, 2011 - November 13, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - TusCon 39, November 9, 2012 - November 11, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - TusCon 40, November 8, 2013 - November 10, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - TusCon 41, October 31, 2014 - November 2, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - TusCon Advertisement Photos, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - TusCon Correspondence, 1977 - 2014 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - TusCon Registration, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - History of TusCon, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous TusCon Materials, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Binder of TusCon 1 - 19 ephemera, 1974 - 1989 (Box 2)
  - Binder of TusCon 20 - 39 ephemera, 1990 - 2012 (Box 2)
  - TusCon Badges and Pins, 1976 - 2012 (Box 3)
- Other Science Fiction Convention Materials, 1972 - 2011; Series 2
  This series is arranged alphabetically, containing the programs, flyers, administrative paperwork, and ephemera from IguanaCon/WorldCon, a convention that Carol De Priest worked on as well as ephemera from various other Arizona-based and regional-based Science Fiction conventions that she attended, including LepreCon, L.A. Con, and CopperCon.
  - Anizona, March 21, 2008 - March 23, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - APA-L 381, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - ARAMCO BRATS, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Arizona Amateur Press Organization - AZAPA 3, July 1975 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Arizona Amateur Press Organization - AZAPA 8, December 1975 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Arizona Amateur Press Organization - AZAPA 11, Spring 1976 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Arizona Science Fiction and Fantasy Guide, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Author Summaries, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Autoclave, May 28, 1976 - May 31, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - BASFA/SASFFA, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bubonicon, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - CactusCon, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Cascadia Con, September 1, 2005 - September 5, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - ConComCon, June 13, 2008 - June 15, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - ConNotations, 1993 - 1995 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - ConNotations, 1996 - 1999 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - ConNotations, 2000 - 2004 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - ConNotations, 2005 - 2006 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - ConNotations, 2007 - 2010 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - CopperCon, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - CoyoteCon, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - DarkCon, 1999 - 2010 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - DesertCon, 1974 - 1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - DisCon, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - FiestaCon, July 2, 2009 - July 5, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - IguanaCon, 1977 - 1978 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - IguanaCon Administration, 1977 - 1978 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - IguanaCon Correspondence, 1977 - 1978 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - IguanaCon Correspondence, 1977 - 1978 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - IguanaCon Registration, 1977 - 1978 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - LA Con, August 30, 1984 - September 3, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - LepreCon, 1978 - 2010 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - LepreCon Programs, 1978 - 1996 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Local Tucson Papers, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - LOCUS, December 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Lone Star Con, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - LosCon, 1978 - 2007 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - MAW, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Metatheatre, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Non-TusCon Materials, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Missing White Girl, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Mountain Newsreal, March 1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - NASFIC, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - North American DiscWorld Convention, September 4, 2009 - September 7, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Notes on Conventions, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Once and Future Nimrod, The, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Orycon, November 11, 1983 - November 13, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Publisher Marketing, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - RinCon, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - SF Convention Register, October 31, 2008 - November 2, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - SMOFCON, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - SolarCon, April 22, 1977 - April 24, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Southern Arizona Fandom News, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Speculations Newsletter, Fall 1981 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Tucson L5 Space Society, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - WesterCon, 1973 - 1992 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - World Fantasy Awards, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - World Fantasy Con, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - World Horror Con, 1994 - 2008 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Non-TusCon Badges, 1978 - 2011 (Box 6)
  - Non-TusCon Pins, undated (Box 7)